thunderztech.com 2018-12-15

# Privacy Policy | ThunderzTech

At www.thunderztech.com, the privacy of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.thunderztech.com and how it is used. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Personal Information**

Like many other Web sites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside thunderztech.com.

**Cookies Policy**

We also use third party advertisements on thunderztech.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site. Google, through their Adsense Program, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to thunderztech.com users based on their visit to this and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

If you require further information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at nkonweb@gmail.com
